export const questionsData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "17 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "10", label: "10" },
      { value: "20", label: "20" },
      { value: "17", label: "17" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "20",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "45 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "50", label: "50" },
      { value: "45", label: "45" },
      { value: "40", label: "40" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "50",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "75 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "70", label: "70" },
      { value: "80", label: "80" },
      { value: "175", label: "175" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "80",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "19 rounded to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "20", label: "20" },
      { value: "10", label: "10" },
      { value: "19", label: "19" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "20",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "64 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "64", label: "64" },
      { value: "70", label: "70" },
      { value: "60", label: "60" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "60",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "0 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "10", label: "10" },
      { value: "1", label: "1" },
      { value: "0", label: "0" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "0",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "98 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "80", label: "80" },
      { value: "100", label: "100" },
      { value: "89", label: "89" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "100",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "199 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "190", label: "190" },
      { value: "100", label: "100" },
      { value: "200", label: "200" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "200",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "94 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "100", label: "100" },
      { value: "94", label: "94" },
      { value: "90", label: "90" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "90",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "165 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "160", label: "160" },
      { value: "170", label: "170" },
      { value: "150", label: "150" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "170",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "445 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "450", label: "450" },
      { value: "440", label: "440" },
      { value: "500", label: "500" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "450",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "999 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
    options: [
      { value: "990", label: "990" },
      { value: "1,000", label: "1,000" },
      { value: "909", label: "909" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "1,000",
  },
];